Julio Cesar Castaño Almanzar

Santo Domingo, Dominican Republic



Julio ccatb@hotmail.com



+1(809)-847-6177



linkedin.com/in/julio-cca

Summary

I am a System Engineer. I have 2 year experience as a developer making desktop applications for companies that need technological alternatives such as inventory controls or information flow between different areas.

I'm currently interested in developing web applications for companies, hoping to continue learning new technologies that contribute to being a much more complete professional.

Experience



Network Administrator

Colégio Loyola

Aug 2021 - Present (1 year 8 months)

- · Structured Cabling
- Technical Support
- Cisco Networking
- VoIP
- Virtualization on Proxmox

Sofware Developer

Ozono Quimicos

Oct 2019 - Present (3 years 6 months)

- App development
- · Web development
- Server management
- Red Architecture

Senior Software Developer

Atabey Center

Jul 2021 - Dec 2021 (6 months)

- Scrum Principles
- CPanel Administration
- · Project Manager
- React Development
- Moodle Implementation
- · Wordpress Implementation

Senior Database Manager

Soluflex

Oct 2019 - Apr 2020 (7 months)

Tecnical Support

- Trainer
- · Company representative

Education

Universidad APEC

Grado en Ingeniería, Ingeniería informática Sep 2017 - Sep 2022

Colegio Dominicano De La Salle

Bachelor's degree, High School/Secondary Diplomas and Certificates Sep 2012 - Jun 2016

Skills

Engineering • Business Development • Data Analytics • English • Research • Supply Chain Management • Programming • Quality Assurance • C# • JavaScript